zibbet.com 2014-06-14

# Privacy Policy

## ZIBBET PRIVACY POLICY

### Our commitment to privacy

At Zibbet Pty Ltd ("zibbet.com"), we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to www.zibbet.com ("the site") need to control the uses of their personal information. www.zibbet.com is a leading online marketplace where people can buy and sell Handmade Goods, Fine Art, Vintage Items and Crafting Supplies, and participate in an online artisan community. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by us to protect your ("you" or "user") privacy in connection with your use of our Site and Services.

### What this policy covers

This privacy policy covers the use of the zibbet.com web site at http://www.zibbet.com, including how Zibbet treats personal information that Zibbet collects and receives. Pursuant to Zibbets’ terms of Use, you must be 16 years and older to use this site or have permission from a legal guardian. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 16 years old.

### Acceptance of privacy policy

Your use of our site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the terms of use. BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

### What information is collected?

You can browse our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers.

Zibbet collects personal information when you register to use Zibbet services or to post content on Zibbet. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information. Zibbet automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request. Zibbet uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. Internet Protocol (IP) addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in Zibbet’s user registration databases when you register with Zibbet. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes.

With your permission, we may collect and store the following personal information:

  * Email address, physical contact information
  * Transactional information based on your activities on the sites such as buying & selling or content you generate that relates to your account
  * Shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item; 
  * Community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us;
  * Other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, IP address and standard web log information

### How is your private information used?

Zibbet will not sell or disclose your name or e-mail address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * Provide the services and customer support you request
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement
  * Customize, measure and improve our services and content
  * Compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

Customized experience - We gather your personally identifiable information to provide you with a customized experience on our Site. Your personally identifiable information helps us tailor the content, services, goods and advertising to your current and future needs.

E-mail Communications - Sellers are automatically subscribed to our 'Seller Newsletter'.  This newsletter will keep you up-to-date with everything you need to know as a Zibbet seller, including new features, information about how to make more sales etc.  At the bottom of these emails is an 'unsubscribe' link.  If you click this, you will automatically be unsubscribed from receiving these emails.  You may subscribe to a number of email services providing information about new features, announcements, special promotions and discounts in your member account section. We will not send you these subscribed emails unless you explicitly consent to receive the mailings by checking the subscriptions boxes. You may unsubscribe from these subscribed emails by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email messages, or by updating your preferences in your user account. Our subscribed emails may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the newsletters, including whether the e-mail was opened and/or what links (if any) were clicked. We will combine such information with other information we have about you and may use this information to improve your experience with our site and/or provide more customized e-mail communications to you according to your subscriber preferences. You may also receive from time to time automated or administrative messages relating to your account and use of your account even if you unsubscribe from all subscribed email options.

### Information sharing and disclosure

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.

We may also share your personal information with:

  * Service providers under contract, who help with our business operations such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards.
  * Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and transaction history.
  * Trusted third parties that are affiliated with Zibbet, but never without asking for your consent and authorization.  

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from undesirable conduct, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

When you post a message, your Zibbet ID or alias is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Zibbet may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Zibbet Terms of Use. Zibbet may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with Zibbet’s Copyright Policy, as Zibbet in Zibbet’s sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

Zibbet will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Zibbet has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Zibbet’s Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. Zibbet will transfer information about you if Zibbet is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Zibbet will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Zibbet web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Paypal

When purchasing any item from Zibbet, payment must be made through Paypal. You can pay directly from your PayPal balance or linked bank account or charge it to your credit card directly. Zibbet does not see or have access to any of your sensitive financial details, like your credit card or bank account numbers.

PayPal is the secure, free, easy way to pay and trusted worldwide. Their Privacy policy can be viewed [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). (https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Zibbet products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Zibbet service. Zibbet uses its own cookies for a number of purposes including to access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Zibbet’s services; display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Zibbet; estimate and report Zibbet’s total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve Zibbet’s content and services.

### Third parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our sites or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Zibbet does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Security

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. We will protect the transmission of credit card information through industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

### IP recognition

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We will use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information.

### Links to other sites

Our Site contains hyperlinks and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. These links are provided for your reference only. We do not control, operate or endorse in any respect information, products or services on such third-party sites and are not responsible for their content. Many third-party sites have their own privacy policies that differ from ours. This privacy policy only covers our Site and does not cover any other site. While we make every effort to keep your information secure, we do not control the policies of other sites.

### Anti-spam, spoofing regulations

As part of the buying and selling process, you may obtain another Zibbet user's email address, shipping address and/or other information. Pursuant to Zibbet’s terms of use agreement, you have a limited license to use this information. This information should only be used for Zibbet-related communications or for Zibbet-facilitated transactions. Zibbet has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Zibbet user to your email or physical mail list.

### Account protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Zibbet password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Zibbet and change your password.

### Forums/chat rooms

If you use a forum or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Zibbet is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Changes to privacy policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

### Contact

If you have any questions or suggestions you can contact support@zibbet.com.

Please post all correspondence to;

Zibbet Pty Ltd  
P.O Box 37  
Narellan, NSW 2567

ABN: 71 128 897 021
